In a world where nobody's watching,
[music]
who are you?
>> I never rush my process. [music] I
always feel that people and clients will
feel whether you are present and sincere
with them.
>> No mask, no switch, just me. Who I am
doesn't depend on the room.
>> Doing right isn't just for the applause.
It's who I am.
>> We don't do it because someone's
actually watching us. We do it because
someone's actually relying on us. I was
raised [music] to keep promises and I
still do.
>> Being consistent in front of people and
also when no one is paying attention.
>> I used to be someone who lacks
confidence, [music]
but now I've become somebody who's more
confident and with a strong mind.
>> I don't really care so much about the
commission. I want my client [music] to
trust me and also value what I provide
and offer.
>> It's about how you do the small things.
It will reflect how you do the bigger
things. People may say that I'm a very
boring person who does the same thing
day after day, but I do what is right. I
value resilience because it's helped me
go through the [music] distance.
>> After so many years, I think I did the
right things. It is the sense of
fulfillment. This becomes [music] my
mission in the industry.
>> The greatest [music] test of character
isn't passing a background check. It's
passing the test of time.
It's a [music] journey because it is
something that we continuously [music]
have to act and do. Whether people are
looking at us, whether there's someone
in front of us, [music] it is something
that we answer to ourself. Our moral
compass
>> accountability is something I value a
lot. It's very important. You build it
by saying no when it matters. Trust
needs to be earned over time. [music]
I always believe that whatever I do, it
has to be for my clients, is for them,
for their family and for their life. I
will protect [music] the downside while
they continue to do whatever they like
in their life.
>> Doing right once is easy, but doing
right again and again every day, that's
where character shows.
>> When the auditor's gone, the camera's
off, and the customer leaves, [music]
what remains is the integrity we build
our business on.
>> I once [music] had this encounter with a
client. So during the application, she
requested that I actually leave out some
pre-existing medical conditions in the
hope to let the uh policy go through. I
told her that ultimately this policy
matters most not at the point of
purchase but at the time of paying. I
don't [music] want the customer the
client to be disadvantaged.
>> Trust
makes me feel a sense of connection with
them and I want to make sure that I do
good. If it's not good enough for my mom
and [music] dad, I won't sell it to any
of my other clients as well.
>> I offer solution that is like truly
beneficial to my clients. And [music] if
the solution doesn't actually benefit, I
won't push for it. I don't chase after
targets. If you want to stay long in
this job, then you must make sure
[music] you must be honest and you must
have integrity. All this cannot be
compromised.
>> The choices we make in the [music]
shadows define the reputation we build
and the light.
this young [music] man. I started out
knowing the mother and uh the mother
want this uh [music] young man to start
with a savings plan. In the savings
plan, I added the u critical [music]
illnesses cover when the cancer onset
time uh he's only 24. throughout the
whole [music] process of the tinyosis
even during his last breath the payout
wasn't very um big pay out but I think
it [music] does help the family a lot
because of cases like that it makes me
hang on there even during the tough time
>> sometimes that comes in a [music]
situation where it's not always the most
favorable for the clients decisions that
[music] we make regardless of whether
client takes up a policy it's a long
journey together.
>> Insurance is more important for the
people who cannot afford this little
premiums [music] that they pay. If
something happens, their family will
actually get a lot more for children's
[music] education. And even for elderly
parents, I know when they feel
protected, they really can go and chase
[music] their dreams. Ultimately at the
end of the year when we look back and
then we review of what [music] are the
good and the bad it's always the good
that outweighs the bad.
>> Your customers may not always see what
you do but they'll always feel the
difference you make.
>> Do unto others what [music] you like
others to do unto you under promise and
overd deliver.
>> They know that I care for them.
>> It's really a lot more about the
consistency I am as a person. Client
doesn't always know [music] what happens
behind the scenes. If it's clean and
honest, they stay.
>> Details are never too small. They mean
everything [music] to me. Caring about
them from the bottom of your heart.
>> It's not what you say. It's about how
safe they feel with you. At the end of
the day, clients actually remember how I
make them feel, not just the
spreadsheets.
>> The clients will remember the feeling
long after the policy is done.
They see you [music] most and how you
act when no one's clapping.
>> At Credential, we believe that doing the
right thing, even when no one is
looking, is what sets us [music] apart.
>> Let's continue to foster the culture of
trust and integrity [music]
together.